thepoplook.com 2017-05-28

# Privacy Policy - Poplook.com

POPLOOK.com ("POPLOOK.com", "we", "our", "us") is a trading name of POPLOOK Sdn. Bhd. (973027-X) (Formerly known as Jam Commerce Sdn. Bhd.). We respect the privacy rights of its online visitors ("you", "your", "yours") and recognise the importance of protecting the information collected about them. 

The following information is provided by POPLOOK.com to enable our online visitors to be fully informed of our Privacy Policies. By visiting POPLOOK.com, you are accepting and consenting to the practices described in this Privacy Policy and the Terms and Conditions.

If you are under 16, we require that you inform a parent or guardian about POPLOOK.com's Privacy Policy and Terms and Conditions as well as requiring their consent to the Privacy Policy and Terms and Conditions before registering or placing an order with POPLOOK.com.

## **What personal information do we collect from you and how?**

POPLOOK.com collects personal information in several ways when you place an order or register for a service offered by POPLOOK.com.

By registering for an account, you are consenting to the collection of your personal data as follows:

  * Email Address
  * Name
  * Date of Birth (optional)

If an order is placed with us, we need to hold personal information including but not limited to your:

  * Name
  * Email address
  * Phone numbers
  * Home address
  * Shipping address
  * Credit/Debit card billing address(es)

Your address and contact number details may be given to our courier for delivery services. These details allow us to process your order and to let you know the status of your order.

## **Marketing opt-in and opt-out provision**

When you register, you will be given the option to opt-in to subscribe to our regular update service. We will send you email alerts for new products, features, enhancements, special offers, contests, events of interest, and one-off marketing promotions. Such alerts may include marketing information about POPLOOK.com, our subsidiaries or selected business partners.

We do not sell or otherwise pass your details to third parties for marketing purposes. Marketing communications you subscribe to will only be sent by POPLOOK.com.

At all times, we will offer you the opportunity to unsubscribe out of any service or update to which you have subscribed, if you change your mind. Any email we send you will contain an easy automated unsubscribe link so that you can opt-out of that subscription. Simply follow the indications in the email.

Besides that, you may log on to your POPLOOK’s account and follow the following steps to unsubscribe:

  1. Click on ‘My Account’
  2. Click on ‘My Personal Information’
  3. Uncheck the subscription box for ‘Mailing List Preference’
  4. Enter your password and click ‘SAVE CHANGES’

## **How you can access and if necessary, change the personal information on POPLOOK.COM**

If for any reason you are concerned that the personal information held by POPLOOK.com is not correct, please visit the website and, after logging into the site using the "Login" link on the home page, your personal information will be made available for review and change in the "My Account" section. Only you or, upon your request, the Customer Care department, may access your personal data from the website using your password and User ID. Information may be changed online within "My Addresses" and "My Personal Information". If you prefer, you may contact us by email at [service@poplook.com](mailto:service@poplook.com) and we will amend your personal details.

## **Safeguarding your personally identifiable information**

We will take reasonable care to maintain appropriate safeguards to ensure the security, integrity and privacy of the information you have provided us with. In addition, we will take reasonable steps to ensure that third party business partners' to whom we transfer any data will provide sufficient protection of that personal information.

## **Where and how to ask questions or file complaints**

If you require further information about our Privacy Policy, please go to the Customer Service and FAQ section of the web site where frequently asked questions (FAQ's) are answered. If you require more information please go to the Customer Service section of the web site and send an email to the relevant POPLOOK.com department. If you wish to talk to a POPLOOK.com customer care representative please call 06 253 2750 or write to: c/o Customer Service Executive, POPLOOK.COM, No 13, Jalan TU 51A, Taman Tasik Utama, 75450 Ayer Keroh, Melaka, Malaysia. You can also email us at [service@poplook.com](mailto:service@poplook.com).

## **Personal Data Protection Notice**

In compliance with the Personal Data Protection Act 2010 and its regulations, this Notice is issued to all our valued customers and/or prospective customers. This Notice explains how POPLOOK collect and handle your personal information in accordance with the Malaysian Personal Data Protection Act 2010.

Please check here for more information on the Personal Data Protection Notice.
